hitachi.com 2007-12-17

# HITACHI : About Personal Information Protection

As a global supplier that can provide total solutions, Hitachi, Ltd. handles a variety of information: including our own technical information, and information entrusted to us by customers. Given this situation, and to ensure that such information is treated with the respect it deserves, Hitachi, Ltd. has established an information control system and is implementing it thoroughly.  
In light of these issues, together with the specification of rules and establishment of a management system, Hitachi, Ltd. has fixed the personal information protection policy given below, informed executive staff and workers, and is striving to protect personal information appropriately by following this policy.

Etsuhiko Shoyama  
President and Chief Executive Officer

For Hitachi, Ltd., personal information is information that is related to existing persons and that can be used to identify specific persons (for example, names, birth dates, numbers assigned to individuals, symbols or other marks, images, or voice recordings, and relevant information). This includes information that cannot be used to identify individuals by itself, but can be used to identify individuals by easy cross-referencing with other data. Personal information is not limited just to information that can identify individuals, but also includes all information that indicates facts, decisions, or evaluations relating to a person's attributes (such as a person's height or build, finances, work type, or position).  
Based on the Personal Information Protection Policy given below, Hitachi, Ltd. will pay detailed attention to, and expend the utmost efforts on, protecting and managing such information.

This "About Personal Information Protection" document establishes the handling of personal customer information by Hitachi, Ltd.

  1. Collecting, Using, and Providing Personal Information

While carefully considering the entrusting of customer information during company activities, Hitachi, Ltd. will handle such information appropriately by establishing a management system for personal information protection for each type of business, and also by following stipulated rules for collecting, using, or providing personal information.

  2. Following Laws and Norms

For the handling of personal information, Hitachi, Ltd. will follow the Japanese laws and norms applicable to the protection of relevant personal information. Also, Hitachi, Ltd. will create and follow personal information management rules that conform to these laws and norms.

  3. Implementing Safety Measures

To ensure the correctness and safety of personal information, in accordance with the rules for information security, Hitachi, Ltd. will implement various measures (such as managing access to personal information, restricting the means for transporting personal information outside the company, and preventing incorrect access from outside the company), and strive to prevent any problems with personal information (such as the loss, destruction, falsification, or leakage of information).

  4. Respecting a Person's Rights Regarding His or Her Personal Information

When a customer makes a request to reveal, correct, or delete his or her own personal information, or seeks to prevent the use or provision of such information, Hitachi, Ltd. will respond with sincerity, respecting the customer's rights related to that personal information.

  5. Establishing Rules for Managing Personal Information Protection, and Making Continual Improvements

Hitachi, Ltd. will make sure that executive staff and workers recognize the importance of personal information protection, and will steadily establish rules for managing personal information to ensure that such information is used appropriately and is protected. These rules will be maintained and improved continually.

  1. In relation to Hitachi, Ltd.'s main business activities for electrical machinery parts, information communication machinery parts, electronic parts manufacturing, and the information services industry, Hitachi, Ltd. will use personal information only to achieve the following listed purposes. However, the business activities of Hitachi, Ltd. are many faceted, and you are recommended to view the websites of each business division.

| a | ) | To execute contracts between a customer and Hitachi, Ltd.  
---|---|---  
b | ) | To contact for discussions or meetings with customers  
c | ) | To provide after-service for products  
d | ) | To send guides for conventions or meetings, or guides for new products  
e | ) | To provide various types of member services  
f | ) | To perform stock-related tasks  
g | ) | To respond to various types of inquiries  
h | ) | To perform analysis to improve products or services, based on surveys  
i | ) | To provide personal information to Hitachi group companies when Hitachi, Ltd. co-operates with a Hitachi group company to carry out some business tasks.  
  
  2. Hitachi, Ltd. will not provide customer personal information to a third party without first obtaining consent from the customer, except in the following circumstances:

a | ) | When required by law  
---|---|---  
b | ) | When required to protect human life, to avoid injury, or to protect assets, and when obtaining customer consent would be difficult.  
c | ) | When required to improve public health or improve the healthy upbringing of children, and when obtaining customer consent would be difficult.  
d | ) | When required to co-operate with the lawful activities of a national agency, local government organization, or person or organization entrusted with such a task, and obtaining customer consent would interfere, or be likely to interfere, with the carrying out of such activities.  
e | ) | When entrusted with the handling of personal information, in the range of activities required to reach the purpose of the use.  
f | ) | When providing personal information to continue business activities when business-related events such as mergers occur.  
  
  3. When required to do so for business activities in which Hitachi, Ltd. is co-operating with Hitachi group companies, Hitachi, Ltd. sometimes provides Hitachi group companies with personal information (such as names, workplaces, home addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses, etc.). In such cases, the customer personal information is provided on paper or electronic media. The customer can request Hitachi, Ltd. to stop the provision of the personal information to a Hitachi group company.

  4. When a customer contacts Hitachi, Ltd. by telephone, the conversation may be recorded to aid accurate replies.

To aid customers use Hitachi, Ltd. websites more conveniently, some Hitachi, Ltd. websites may use cookies or web beacons (clear GIF).  
By adjusting their web browser settings, customers can refuse cookies or display warnings when cookies are installed. For details, see the documentation for your web browser. By refusing to accept cookies, customers can refuse web beacons.  
However, please understand that a refusal to use cookies may prevent usage of all or part of the services provided by the Hitachi, Ltd. website.

### Terms

*1 | Cookie  
---|---  
  | A cookie is piece of information that enables interaction between the web server that manages a website and a customer's web browser. A cookie may be stored as a file on the customer's computer disk.  
When a cookie is used, the web server can record information such as which computer visited which pages on the website. However, Hitachi, Ltd. cannot identify an individual customer unless the customer enters his or her own personal information into the website.  
*2 | Web beacon  
  | This technology, which functions with a cookie, enables the beacon owner to know how many times a customer accessed a particular page. However, unless the customer enters his or her own personal information when, or after, the cookie is accepted, Hitachi, Ltd. cannot identify an individual customer.  
  
For customer personal information maintained by Hitachi, Ltd., please carry out the following when requesting Hitachi, Ltd. to reveal, correct, add, delete, stop usage of, stop providing to a third party, or provide a purpose-of-use report for personal information (hereafter, collectively referred to as "reveal, etc."), or when sending a complaint:

  1. For requests to reveal, etc., personal information provided by a customer to business staff of Hitachi, Ltd.:

  2. For requests to reveal, etc., personal information provided by a customer in a Hitachi, Ltd. website:

  3. For requests to reveal, etc., personal information other than for the above cases (1 and 2):

  4. For complaints relating to Hitachi, Ltd.'s handling of personal information:

### Complaints Contact Location

Hitachi, Ltd.  
Maru-no-uchi 1-6-6  
Chiyoda ku,  
Tokyo  
Japan    100-8280

  1. Most of the services provided by Hitachi, Ltd. can be used without requiring customer personal information. However, please understand that some services cannot be provided unless the customer provides personal information to Hitachi, Ltd.

  2. Please understand that Hitachi, Ltd. is not responsible for the safety of personal information at websites of other companies which are linked to the website of Hitachi, Ltd.

  3. It is assumed that the customer agrees to the contents of this "About Information Protection" document when the customer enters personal information into a Hitachi, Ltd. website. If the customer does not agree with this "About Information Protection" document, the customer may be unable to use some of the Hitachi, Ltd. services (including responses to inquiries, etc.).

  1. The personal information protection policy of Hitachi, Ltd. is based on Japanese law.

  2. Hitachi, Ltd. may modify this "About Information Protection" document as appropriate to accommodate improvements in the handling of personal information, or changes or additions to laws or other norms.

  3. This "About Personal Information Protection" document goes into effect from the day it is published (including the update day).

  4. If statements in this document are covered by individual regulations regarding personal information, those regulations take precedence.

To make requests to reveal, etc., personal information (excluding complaints), please use the "[Inquiry Entry Form](https://websign.hitachi.co.jp/form-cgi/inquiry/privacy-e/toiawase.cgi)". Alternatively, you can contact us by [email (kojinjoho@hitachi.co.jp)](mailto:kojinjoho@hitachi.co.jp). When contacting us by email, please clearly enter the same information that is required for entries into the online form.

* | Personal information sent to the above contact addresses is not preserved by Hitachi, Ltd., and is deleted when a reply is made to the inquiry.  
---|---  
  
Enactment date: 2005/04/01
